http://www.cartoonnetwork.com/legal/privacy.html

cartoon network
games v
Teen Titans Go!
video v
Teen Titans Go!
PRIVACY POLICY
CARTOON NETWORK CHILDREN'S PRIVACY POLICY Last updated: July 1, 2020 This Privacy Policy is about how Cartoon Network, a Warner Bros. property, will collect and use any information you give us when you use our Services.  The word “Services” in this Privacy Policy means our websites, mobile apps, games, and other online services. If you need help understanding this document, you should ask the adult who looks after you to read it and talk with you about it. Some of our websites and mobile apps are for adults as well as children. If you are an adult, you should take a look at our general audience Warner Bros. Privacy Policy (https://policies.warnerbros.com/privacy/) for more information about how we will collect and use your data, including on Services that link to  this policy. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT FROM YOU? Information about you For some of our Services, you don’t need to give us information like your name or email address to use the Service.   For some of our Services, we will ask for some more information from you so you can use the Service. We might need to ask permission from the adult who looks after you before you can give us this information.  This can include things like:  - your first name - your location  - your email address - your username  - your telephone number - your home address - numbers that identify your account or device - a photo or video of you For some of our Services, such as virtual worlds, you can play games, talk with your friends or get items, such as gems and additional costumes or powers for your character. For these Services you need to choose a nickname or create an account. You will need to create a username and password and fill out other information about you.  For some Services, we collect your email address to help you make an account and then we keep your email address only in a “hashed” format so that it doesn’t identify you.  We use these “hashed” email addresses to help with your account, like to help you if you forget your password.    Information about your adult Sometimes, we need to collect information about the adult who looks after you. For example, we do this so we can: - let them know about your interest in the Services - ask them for permission so you can access parts of our Services - tell them how to start some of the features for you When we need to contact the adult who looks after you, we will need to get some information from them, so we may ask for their:  - full name  - address - email address - telephone number When you buy things Before buying something, you should always have permission from the adult who looks after you. When you buy something in a Service, your adult may have to pay for it with real money. Some of our Services allow you to buy things inside the Service, pay to join our clubs, and use online money from our Services.  When you talk with your friends Some of our Services will let you talk with your friends in a way that shows your conversation with other people on the Service. Usually, you will choose from phrases we have already written. Otherwise, we will look at the messages so no one uses any bad words or shares your personal information. If we see that you are sharing your personal information with someone else, we will try to delete it before it is shared. We may ask permission from the adult who looks after you before we let you talk to your friends on our Services or if our Services let you post on social media. Information about your computer, console or smartphone When you visit or use one of our Services, we will get some information about your device and your internet browser (for example, Internet Explorer, Chrome or Firefox). We will also get some information about your IP Address and how you use our Services. To learn more, see our section about Cookies. Notifications Our apps may send you alerts from inside the app on your device to help you use the app. For some of our apps, you can also choose to receive notifications on your device that are sent from outside your device (called push notifications). We may need to ask permission from the adult who looks after you to collect the information that we need to send you these push notifications. You can always turn push notifications off in the settings of your device. This might be difficult, so make sure to ask the adult who looks after you to help. When you contact us If you contact us by email or using an online form, we will ask you for some information. For example, this may include your first name and email address. We will also ask you to tell us why you are contacting us. Once we have helped you, we will delete your information. HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION We use your information for different reasons. Where we enter into a contract with you or your parent or guardian For us to provide our services in accordance with their terms of use, we need to use some of your information: - to let you know if those terms or our policies are changing - to give you access to our services, or other things you can receive or connect to through our services - to register you for games or competitions and make sure their rules are followed - to handle purchases and other things you or your parent or guardian order and any related messages about those If you don't provide the necessary information, we will not be able to do these things for you. Where we have a legitimate interest  When using your information is very important to us but still fair to you, we have something called a "legitimate interest". When we have a legitimate interest and we use your information, we need to be sure that it is not going to upset you. We will use your information for our legitimate interest only if the laws of your country allow this.  In some countries, we may need to ask for your consent or the consent of the adult who looks after you before we can use your information in these ways. For example, we have a legitimate interest when we give you access: - to our Services - to play games - to chat with your friends - to post or send us comments We also have a legitimate interest, so we can: - learn how we can make our Services better - make sure your experience can be special and personalized for you - keep you and others safe - answer your questions and comments when you contact us If you and/or the adult who looks after you gives us permission (consent) If you are old enough, you can give us permission to use your information. If you are not old enough, you will sometimes need to ask the adult who looks after you for permission. For example, when you want to receive a newsletter.  If the law says we must use your information If the law says we must use your information, then we will do so. For example: - if the government or the police need to investigate something - if the law says we need to use your information HOW DO WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION? Our helpers (service providers) Sometimes we have helpers who make sure our Services are great. They will help operate the Services or help with buying things on our Services, like points. They will also help with sending prizes to competition winners. We make sure that our helpers keep your information safe. Our friends (for example, co-sponsors) Sometimes we ask our friends to help us with our Services. If we do, they will have access to your information. We will let you know when we ask our friends to help us. Our family (affiliates) Sometimes we may share information with members of our family that agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. You can find a list of some of the Warner Bros. Entertainment Group companies and affiliated WarnerMedia companies by visiting our affiliates’ page (https://policies.warnerbros.com/privacy/en-us/affiliates/html/affiliates_en-us_2.4.0.html). We may update this list from time-to-time, so please check back periodically to keep up-to-date.  Links to other people's websites (external links) Our Services will sometimes have links to other people's websites. Those people can treat your information differently from us. You should make sure you understand how they will use your information by looking at their privacy policies. Sharing information  When we have your adult’s permission for you to use social media platforms or plugins on our Services, those platforms can share their information back to the social media platform. This can mean that your friends will be told about what you do on our Service. You and the adult who looks after you should look at the privacy policies of these social media sites to learn more about how they use information about you. If the law says we must share your information Warner Bros., our friends and our helpers will sometimes need to share your information with other people when the law says so. For example, this can happen if the police, a judge, or the government asks us to. We need to share your information if it will help us stop people from doing bad things or committing crimes. We also need to share your information if it will help us protect you or other people. If we sell or reorganize our business If we sell or reorganize our business, we will share your information with the buyer or entity taking over operation of the Service. If you or the adult who looks after you gives us permission If you or the adult who looks after you gives us permission to share your information for something, then we will share your information in the way we describe at the time. COOKIES What are cookies? Cookies are tiny files that have information (data) in them. Sometimes we use other types of digital technologies, but they work a lot like cookies. When you visit our Services, a cookie is placed on your device (like your computer, console or smartphone). Some mobile apps have technology that works like cookies. Cookies do not hurt your device.  What do cookies do? Cookies help us to make your experience better. They can remember what you do on the Service (like your high score) and help us understand what you like doing.  The cookies will also help us know which parts of the Services are popular and which ones we need to make better. Some of our helpers and friends use their own cookies or other technology to help us or for their own activities. For example, these can help us understand how many people visited a Service. Turning cookies off You can choose to turn cookies off. You can also choose to block all cookies. You can do this using the settings menu. This might be difficult so make sure to ask the adult who looks after you to help you.  If you do choose to turn cookies off, somethings on the website or Service might not work properly or your experience might not be as good. Some of our Services use a helper called Google Analytics. You have to turn off their cookies in a different way. To learn how to turn off their cookies, by visiting the Google Analytics Cookie Usage Website [https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage]. You can also get the adult who looks after you to install a plug-in so they can take control of Google Analytics cookies. They can do this by visiting the Google tool website at [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en]. SENDING YOUR INFORMATION AROUND THE WORLD We have offices around the world. Sometimes, we will need to send your information to a different country. Usually, this is to the United States where Warner Bros. and our helpers will use your information in the way we have already described in this Privacy Policy. It is important to remember that some countries do not have laws that protect your information in the same way. If you or the adult who looks after you want more information about how we send your information around the world, you can contact us by using the information at the end of this Privacy Policy. WE WANT TO KEEP YOUR INFORMATION SAFE We take reasonable steps to protect your information to stop other people getting to it. We also make sure to not keep your information for too long. If we need your information for our own purposes, we will also keep your information for three years after you last contact our customer support team or interact with our websites and apps or after you stop being subscribed or registered with us. Sometimes the law says we have to keep your information for longer than this. We may have to keep your information for longer to protect you and us.  When it’s time for us to stop keeping your information, we will burn or shred hard copies (like print-outs) and delete electronic copies in a way that means no one can read that information. We may need to send you a message if someone gets to your information without our permission.  We will usually send this message by email to you or the adult who takes care of you.  Our message will explain what happened, why this matters to you, and what we are doing to fix it.  If we cannot send you this message directly, we may make a public post about it. YOUR RIGHTS You or the adult who looks after you can ask to access your information, ask us to delete it, or stop us from using it sometimes. Sometimes they can even ask us to fix any mistakes or send it to someone else. Where we have asked the adult who looks after you to agree to let us use your information, they can stop us from using it. You or your adult can make these requests through our online portal by visiting our Privacy Center. [https://privacycenter.wb.com/] CONTACT US If you or the adult who looks after you have any questions about this Privacy Policy you can contact us through our online portal by visiting our Privacy Center [https://privacycenter.wb.com/] or write to us at the following address: Warner Bros. Entertainment Inc. Attention: Chief Privacy Officer  4000 Warner Blvd., Bldg. 160 Burbank, CA 91522  United States 833-WB-PRVCY (833-927-7829) or 833-PRVCY-TT (833-778-2988) wmprivacy@warnermediagroup.com UPDATES From time to time, we may update this Privacy Policy. We will let you know about any big changes to how we use your information by putting a sign on our website or by sending the adult who looks after you an email message. We think it is a good idea for you to come back to this page once in a while to learn about how we protect your information. CALIFORNIA AND CCPA PRIVACY RIGHTS AND DISCLOSURES If you need help understanding the California and CCPA Privacy Rights and Disclosures section, you should ask the adult who looks after you to read it and talk with you about it. This California and CCPA Privacy Rights and Disclosure section was last updated July 1, 2020 and addresses legal obligations and rights laid out in the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) and other laws that apply only to California residents. These obligations and rights apply to businesses doing business in California and to California residents and information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with California consumers or households (“California Information”). It does not apply to information that has been de-identified or aggregated as provided by CCPA. CALIFORNIA INFORMATION WE COLLECTED AND SHARED This section provides the information California residents need to exercise their rights over their California Information. Here is information about the California Information we have collected from and shared about consumers in the year before this section was last updated. California Information We Collected In the year before this section was last updated, we may have collected the following categories of California Information, as legally permitted: - Address and other identifiers – such as name, phone number, postal address, zip code, email address, account name or number, date of birth, or other similar identifiers - Unique and other online identifiers – such as IP address, device IDs, or other similar identifiers that relate to your device and its operating system - Commercial information – such as products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies - Internet or other electronic network activity information – such as browsing history, search history, and information regarding your interactions with our Services, and content such as videos, ads, websites, and devices such as smart TVs, streaming media, browsers and apps - Audio, visual, or similar information – such as photos, videos, or recordings you or a parent or guardian may choose to post to our Services - Location information – such as your device’s general location in connection with certain Services  - Inferences or audience segmentation – such as individual profiles, preferences, characteristics, and behaviors - In-Game or online viewing activities – such videos, content, and pages viewed We may have collected these categories of California Information for the following business or commercial purposes: - Performing services on behalf of the business – such as customer service, processing or fulfilling orders, providing content recommendations, and processing payments - Auditing customer transactions - Fraud and crime prevention - Debugging errors in systems - Marketing and advertising on the Service based on what you are watching or browsing - Internal research, analytics and development – e.g., user-preference analytics - Developing, maintaining, provisioning or upgrading networks, products, services, or devices We may have obtained California Information from a variety of sources, including:  - Directly from you – such as technical and usage information when you use our Site - Linked sites – such as social media sites and third-party platforms - Our affiliates  - Our joint ventures and promotional and strategic partners  - Information suppliers - Distributors and other vendors - Other users submitting information about you – such as to invite you to participate in an offering, make recommendations, or share content - Publicly available sources  Disclosures of California Information: In the year before this section was last updated, we may have disclosed the following categories of California Information to third parties as legally permitted: - Address and other identifiers – such as name, phone number, postal address, zip code, email address, account name or number, date of birth, or other similar identifiers - Unique and other online identifiers – such as IP address, device IDs, or other similar identifiers that relate to your device and its operating system - Commercial information – such as products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies - Internet or other electronic network activity information – such as browsing history, search history, and information regarding your interactions with our Services, and content such as videos, ads, websites, and devices such as smart TVs, streaming media, browsers and apps - Audio, visual, or similar information – such as photos, videos, or recordings you or a parent or guardian may choose to post to our Services  - Location information – such as your device’s general location in connection with certain Services - Inferences or audience segmentation – such as individual profiles, preferences, characteristics, and behaviours - In-Game or online viewing activities – such videos, content, and pages viewed We may have disclosed each of these categories of California Information to the following categories of third parties: - Affiliates – These entities are associated with us through common ownership.  For a list of affiliates, visit our affiliates’ page (https://policies.warnerbros.com/privacy/en-us/affiliates/html/affiliates_en-us_2.4.0.html - Service Providers – These entities process information on our behalf for business purposes, helping us provide products or services to you - Social Media Platforms – These entities maintain networks connecting individuals and organizations on some of our Services - Advertising Partners – These entities help us advertise products or services on the Service based on what you are watching or browsing - Analytics Partners – These entities help us collect data on how our products or services are used, so that we can improve them and better understand our consumers - Promotional Partners – We partner with these entities to jointly promote our products, for example by running contests or other promotional campaigns - Government Entities – These entities include law enforcement authorities, regulatory agencies, and courts YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS TO REQUEST DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND SHARE ABOUT YOU If you are a California resident, the CCPA grants you the right to request certain information about our practices with respect to California Information. In particular, you can request the following: - The categories and specific pieces of your California Information that we’ve collected - The categories of sources from which we collected California Information - The business or commercial purposes for which we collected California Information - The categories of third parties with which we shared California Information You can submit a request to us for the following additional information: - The categories of third parties to whom we’ve disclosed California Information, and the category or categories of California Information disclosed to each  YOUR RIGHT TO REQUEST THE DELETION OF CALIFORNIA INFORMATION Upon your request, we will delete the California Information we have collected about you, except for situations when that information is necessary for us to: provide you with a product or service that you requested; perform a contract we entered into with you; maintain the functionality or security of our systems; comply with or exercise rights provided by the law; or use the information internally in ways that are compatible with the context in which you provided the information to us, or that are reasonably aligned with your expectations based on your relationship with us. WE DO NOT SELL YOUR CALIFORNIA INFORMATION HOW TO EXERCISE YOUR CALIFORNIA RIGHTS You may exercise your rights to request access to or deletion of your California Information by contacting us at our Privacy Center ( https://privacycenter.wb.com/) You can also contact us toll free at 833-WB-PRVCY (833-927-7829) or TTY: 833-PRVCY-TT (833-778-2988) and an agent will assist you with submitting a request.  These requests are generally free. When you submit a request, we will usually ask you to provide an email address which we will contact to confirm the request was not fraudulently submitted. In addition, for access and deletion requests, we will use a third-party verification service to confirm that you are who you say you are.  Our verification service does this by matching information you provide against information held about you in its records, or, if necessary, by allowing you to submit documents proving your identity. If you are the parent of a child under 13 years of age, you may also submit a request on behalf of your child.  In that event, we will ask you to provide your child’s email address, to verify your identity, and to submit a signed form authorizing us to proceed with the request regarding your child’s California Information.  You may also designate an authorized agent to submit a request on your behalf.  To do so, we will require either (1) a valid power of attorney, or (2) signed written permission from you.  In the event your authorized agent is relying on signed written permission, we may also need to verify your identity and/or contact you directly to confirm permission to proceed with the request. Your authorized agent can make a request by contacting us toll free at 833-WB-PRVCY (833-927-7829) or TTY: 833-PRVCY-TT (833-778-2988). OUR SUPPORT FOR THE EXERCISE YOUR DATA RIGHTS You have the right not to receive discriminatory treatment if you exercise any of the rights explained in this section of the Privacy Policy.  We are committed to providing you control over your California Information, we will not disadvantage you if you choose to exercise your rights.   CALIFORNIA CONSUMERS UNDER 16 YEARS OLD CCPA has specific rules regarding the use of California Information from consumers under 16 years of age.  In particular, consistent with the CCPA, if we knowingly collect the California Information of a consumer under the age of 16, we will not sell the information unless we receive affirmative permission to do so.  If the consumer is between the ages of 13 and 16 years of age, the consumer may provide that permission; if the consumer is under the age of 13, the consumer’s parent or guardian must provide the permission. As of the Effective Date of this Privacy Policy, we do not have actual knowledge that we sell California Information of consumers under 16 years of age. If you would like further information on how we handle California Information from consumers under the age of 16 years of age, or if you have questions about these information practices, you may contact us at wmprivacy@warnermediagroup.com, or at WarnerMedia Privacy Office, 4000 Warner Blvd., Bldg. 160, Burbank, CA 91522. CALIFORNIA CONSUMERS UNDER 18 YEARS OLD California consumers who are registered users of the Sites and under 18 years of age may request removal of content or information they posted on the Sites. We will remove such content or information when we are required to do so by law. To request removal of content or information you posted on the Sites, you may contact us at wmprivacy@warnermediagroup.com, or at WarnerMedia Privacy Office, 4000 Warner Blvd., Bldg. 160, Burbank, CA 91522.  However, even if we remove the content or information that you posted, we cannot completely prevent further use or disclosure of that content or information by others once you have shared it in a publicly available forum.
Privacy Policy
Terms of Use
Closed Captioning
TVE Parental Controls
Trademark
Help
Contact Us
Use of this site signifies your agreement to the Terms of Use. TM &mp © 2020 Cartoon Network. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved. CartoonNetwork.com is part of Turner Entertainment Digital which is part of the Turner Sports &mp Entertainment Digital Network.
